You know, I End myself wondering
(Sheldon:)if anything you've
ever told me is true.
(Leonard:)I didn't make it back.
The ship sank, I'm in hell.
(Sheldon:)You say you're from New Jersey,
but how can I believe you?
(Leonard:)Why would anyone claim to be
from New Jersey if they weren't?
(Sheldon:)All right, I'll give you that one.
(Leonard:)Hey, I said I was sorry.
What else do you want from me?
(Sheldon:)I want you to admit that
what you did was wrong.
(Leonard:)Fine. What I did was wrong.
(Sheldon:)I wish I could believe you.
(Penny:)You know what?
I'm not driving you to work,
(Leonard:)because you're incredibly annoying.
(Sheldon:)You say one thing and do the other,
(Sheldon:)so then you are driving me
and you find me a delight.
(Bernadette:)-Stop it.
-Keep it up?
-B!/eg
-Hello!